https://www.wesbanco.com/privacy-notice/

Rev. 5/2016
What does WesBanco do with your personal information?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What information?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and income
Assets and account balances
Payment history and credit history
How do we use it?
All financial companies need to share customer personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customer personal information; the reasons WesBanco chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does WesBanco share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
Yes
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates to market to you
Yes
Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
To limit our sharing:
Print/Download this form and Mail it in to:
WesBanco Bank, Inc.
Attn: Bank Operations
One Bank Plaza
Wheeling, West Virginia 26003
Please note:
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?
Call: 800-905-9043
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
WesBanco Bank, Inc., WesBanco Bank Community Development Corporation, WesBanco Securities, Inc., WesBanco Insurance Services, Inc., WesBanco Title Agency, LLC, and WesMark Funds
What we do
How does WesBanco protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does WesBanco collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account or apply for a loan
Give us your contact information or give us your income information
Provide identifying information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account — unless you tell us otherwise.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
Our affiliates include companies with a WesBanco name and investment companies such as WesMark Funds.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
WesBanco does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners include credit card companies.
I'd Like More Info About...*
I'd Like More Info About...*Personal CheckingPersonal SavingsLoans & Credit CardsMortgage or RefinancingInvestmentsInsuranceCustomer ServiceOther
WesBanco Bank, Inc.Routing Number:
IN, KY, OH, PA, & WV: 043400036MD: 055002406
NMLS ID Number:
399836
Copyright © 2020 · WesBanco, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Notice |
Security Center | Site by Vitamin®
WesBanco Bank, Inc. is a Member FDIC. Equal Housing Lender
